Camfrog Privacy Policy
----------------------

### Effective November 24, 2020

Camfrog values our users privacy and protection of their data, we build our apps and operate our business with this in mind.

Camfrog is a property of Paltalk Inc. who also operates Paltalk, TinyChat, and Vumber. Your services are provided by Paltalk Inc. who also acts as a data controller for your information.

By using Camfrog you are also using its sister product Ribbit which is a mobile video viewing application. In this policy when we mention Camfrog this will also include use and interaction with Ribbit.

This privacy policy applies to all of Camfrog’s services. By using Camfrog you agree to this Privacy Policy as well as our [Terms of Service](https://www.camfrog.com/en/terms.phtml).

As part of providing a great experience for you this sometimes requires us to collect personal information from you. We have done our best to give you control and access to your data where possible and we want you to be aware how that data is being used. This policy will cover:

* What information we may collect about you
* What we may do with the information we collect about you
* Whether we share your information with anyone else
* How we use cookies on our site
* Where we store your information
* How we keep your information secure
* Your rights in relation to your information

At Paltalk Inc. we take your privacy seriously. We operate on the principle that your personal information belongs to you and only you can decide who you want to share it with and why. This is fundamental to the way we work and we’re committed to providing a secure environment for you to store your personal information and share it with others when you want to.

#### Information you voluntarily provide

To register and interact with members on the site, many times you will be prompted to share information with us to improve your experience while using the product. Some of the information you may share with us includes:

* User nickname
* E-mail address
* Address or location information
* Birthdate
* Gender
* Interests
* Payment information
* Photos
* Personal description
* Shared social network details
* Information to customer support
* Mobile Number
* Name
* Use of your Camera
* Use of your Microphone
* Recorded Video

We primarily use this information to help other users find and connect with you, if you want to update this information you can visit your [profile](https://profiles.camfrog.com/home.php) at any time to do so. If you specifically desire, we will use your social networking data to allow you to create an account with data you have on another site. Your payment information is used when you decide to purchase premium parts of the Service. Information shared with customer support will be used solely to address the issue(s) you have brought to our attention. Use of your camera and microphone are optional; when using your microphone or camera in a chatroom, it will share video or audio to other users in that room.

#### Information we collect about you and your device

When you use Camfrog and interact with our services, we may use technology to collect information about your activity. Some of the data that is collected while using the website and mobile/desktop clients may include:

* IP address
* Type of browser you use
* Number of sessions per browser/client on each device
* Type of device and operating system
* Referrer information
* Local language
* Actions taken while in the client or on the website
* Device identifiers

We use this information to help tailor your experience for your device/language. We also use this information to help prevent fraud as well as identify service issues.

#### This is what we do with the information we collect about you

We use the information you provide to us to:

* Enable us to provide the Services
* Ensure that our apps/website are presented in an effective manner for you and for your device
* Provide you with marketing information about us and our services ([Opt Out](https://profiles.camfrog.com/settings.php#tab-information))
* Notify you about changes to Camfrog
* Carry out our obligations arising out of the Terms of Service
* Defend our servers against malicious attacks

We try to be as careful as possible when using your data. Anywhere we take in personal data or perform actions we feel may be optional or objectionable to you, we will ask for your consent which can also be revoked at a later date. We are always looking to improve and as we identify data that falls into this category will continue to add new messaging to you so you are always aware of when we take in your data and how we process it.

At times on Camfrog you may be shown content from YouTube or interact with the YouTube API. Please see Google's [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) for more information on how Youtube and Google handle your data.

The law gives you the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you. We may request additional information about you to verify your identity before we do such. We will supply, correct or delete personal information about you in our files. In addition, you may request rectification or erasure of personal information as well as the restriction of processing of your personal information. We will comply with your requests in accordance with the applicable law.

Camfrog respects a user's wishes to delete their personal data. At any time a user may deactivate their account by visiting [this link](https://profiles.camfrog.com/profiles/deactivate), your account deletion will also remove your personal data. If you have any issues or questions while attempting to delete your account you may also contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.camfrog.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) for additional assistance.

#### Information Collection & Use

##### Registration

In order to use Camfrog, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give contact information such as your email address. We use this information to contact you about services on our site in which you have expressed interest. Please see below for Information and Sharing Disclosure.

##### Communications from the Site

* **Special Offers and Updates**
    
    We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, or promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out."
    
* **Newsletters**
    
    If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section.
    
* **Service-related Announcement**
    
    We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

RESOURCES
---------

SUPPORT
-------

LEGAL
-----

* Cookie Settings

SOCIAL
------

OUR PRODUCTS
------------

ABOUT US
--------

English

###### CHANGE LANGUAGE

* العربية
* Bosanski
* Deutsch
* Français
* Bahasa Indonesia
* Italiano
* 한국어, 조선말
* Русский
* ภาษาไทย
* Türkçe
* 中文, 汉语
* 中文, 漢語

© 2003— Camshare Inc.
